racingone.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy - MRN - Motor Racing Network

**We are always conscious and respectful of your personal privacy.**

This Privacy Policy governs the use of the MotorRacingNetwork.com (“MRN”) website (the “Site”).  The Privacy Policy’s purpose is to make you aware of our privacy policy and practices and the way information is collected and used with respect to the Site. To make this notice easy to find, a link to this Privacy Policy is on the homepage of the Site.  This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect at the Sites, but does not apply to information collected through other means.

This Privacy Policy will answer your questions about the kind of information we collect and how we use it. If we change or update our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here.  By using this Site, you acknowledge you have read this Privacy Policy and agree to the terms hereof.

**What information do you gather and how do you use it?**

MRN automatically collects certain non-personally identifiable information about your visits to the Site, such as IP address, service provider, browser type, operating system, pages accessed on the Site and the date and time of access to optimize your user experience and enhance your time spent with us online. Each owner also receives information telling us what site from which you originated.

When you send MRN an e-mail, MRN will retain the content of the e-mail, your e-mail address, and our response in order to handle any follow-up questions you may have. MRN also uses this information to measure how effectively MRN addresses your concerns.

When purchasing tickets or merchandise, joining as a member, registering for promotions at the Site, or in connection with gifts, ecards, e-vites, forward-to-a-friend messages or any other messaging service, MRN may ask for your or your friend’s:

  * Name
  * E-mail address
  * Credit card number and expiration date
  * Billing address
  * Shipping address
  * Date of Birth
  * Phone number

The foregoing shall be referred to as “personal information.”  We use the personally identifiable information you choose to provide to MRN to process the transactions and services you request, to provide MRN and MRN affiliates promotional communications to you, to enable you to participate in sweepstakes and promotions, and to otherwise facilitate your use of the Site.

MRN may ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experiences with us, and contact preferences.  This information may be combined with information about you, which MRN gathered from other offline sources. MRN and its affiliates use the information to design offers customized to your interests. For example, you may receive a special offer for your most frequently visited events.

I **nformation from other sources**

MRN may receive information about you from other sources.  This may help improve the personalization of our service to you by providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you.

**Who do you share my personal information with?**

MRN may share your name and personal information with its affiliate companies for such affiliates to send you promotional communications such as emails, phone calls and newsletters. MRN may also share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties (such as third party sponsors or sanctioning bodies i.e. NASCAR) that wish to market their products or services to you.  MRN may share anonymous, aggregated information (information that does not individually identify a user) about all our users with third parties for any lawful purpose.

**Service providers**

MRN may also share personal information with companies that provide support services to us (such as a printer, mailing house or web host) or that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose.

**Protection of the Site and others**

MRN may disclose information you provide at the Site when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of the Site, our users or other individuals.

**How does this Site use cookies and similar tracking technologies?**

This Site uses cookies, tags, pixels and similar tracking technologies to allow MRN to recognize your preference information, keep track of your purchases, remember your Member Login and facilitate effective site administration. MRN uses the information we collect to enhance your visit to this site and provide you with information tailored to your needs.

You may elect to refuse cookies, but certain Site functions or access may not be available if you choose to do so. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies. This Site does not change its behavior based on the presence of a “Do Not Track” header/request sent from a user device.  In addition, third party tracking pixels may or may not adjust their behavior based on the presence of a “Do Not Track” header/request, this is under the control of the respective third party.  Any such tracking does not share any personally identifiable information, but only marks/tags a user to receive related information while visiting other websites in the same tracking network.

A Web beacon is an electronic image, also called a single-pixel or clear GIF, placed in the code of a webpage or in e-mails.  The Site uses Web beacons to track traffic patterns of users as they navigate from one page to another.  This information lets us tune and improve our users’ browsing experience.  As with cookies, the information that Web beacons collect is aggregated, anonymous “click stream” data, and is not associated with you as an individual.

We also use Web beacons through a third party website analytics provider, as well as standard Web server log files, to help us count visitors and evaluate the Site’s technical capacity.  This information tells us how many people visit the Site, and helps us decide how to arrange pages in the most user-friendly way.  This also helps us keep the Site browser-friendly and more useful to our users.  We record information on Site traffic, but not on individual visitors to the Site, so no personal information about you will be kept or used.

**How does this Site comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act?**

The Website is not intended for use by children under 13 years of age.  MRN does not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 13 years of age, except for the limited circumstances described below.  In the event a child under the age of 13 submits a question to us on the Site and identifies his or her age, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit our use of the child’s email address for the sole purpose of responding to the child’s question on a one-time-only basis.  However, we will not use the child’s email address to re-contact the child and we will delete it from our records once we have responded.  If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**What choices do I have regarding** **promotional communications?**

MRN only sends promotional e-mail messages to you if you have voluntarily provided MRN with your e-mail address. Further, by providing your email address you agree that MRN may share such information with MRN affiliates and that such MRN affiliates may directly send you promotional materials.  You may request to be removed from this Site’s e-mail subscription list by updating your personal account.  By clicking on the “Member Name” link at the top of the page you can access your personal account to make the necessary changes. You may also unsubscribe from any e-mail subscription by following the unsubscribe procedures set forth in each e-mail, including those received from MRN affiliates.

**How do I update personal information such as my address?**

MRN asks that you keep your information as up-to-date as possible so you may get the maximum benefit from this Site. By clicking on the “Member Name” link at the top of the page you can access your personal account to make the necessary changes.

**What about security at the Site?**

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable federal privacy and data security laws and regulations to guard your personal information.  Unfortunately, no transmissions or data available through the Internet can be 100% secure and, accordingly, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any personal information or other information you provide to us.  MRN works to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. MRN reveals only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, MRN transmits the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**What about links to and from other websites**

This Site may offer links to other websites, or you may have arrived at this Site from websites, that are operated by entities other than MRN.  These third party websites have their own policies regarding privacy. If you visit one of these websites, or if you arrived from one of these websites, you should review the privacy policy of the website to understand how your personal information is collected, used, secured and disclosed. MRN is not responsible for the privacy practices of these third party websites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected, used or shared there.

**Business transfers**

If some or all of the business assets of MRN or the Site are sold or transferred, your personal information, aggregated information, and any other information that we have collected in connection with the Site may be transferred as part of our business assets.  In such case, we also may retain a copy of this information.

**Community Feature**

Any information, including Personal Information, that you contribute to a public area or feature of the Site, such as a user forum, blog, wiki or other open forum on the Site, will be made available to the general public.  Therefore, we recommend that you do not submit any sensitive Personal Information to these public forums.  MRN is not responsible for the Personal Information or other information you choose to submit to these forums.

**International Users**

As this Site is operated from the United States and our computer systems are currently based in the United States, personal information submitted at the Site will be processed by MRN in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union.  By providing personal information at this Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States.

By using this Site, you signify your assent to the MRN Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the MRN Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site. We reserve the right, at our complete discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time.

Revised:  May 21, 2018

**Contact Information for MRN:**

Postal address: One Daytona Blvd.

Daytona Beach, FL 32114

Attention: Webmaster

Telephone (386) 254-2700

Email:  feedback@mrn.com

**EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) – European Economic Area member country (the EEA), Switzerland and United Kingdom (UK) Users Only**

Beginning May, 25, 2018, the GDPR requires us to provide you with certain information regarding the processing of your personal information.

Legal Basis for Processing Personal Information:

The legal basis for our processing of your personal information is generally because: (a) you have consented to our processing of such personal information, (b) it is necessary for us to perform our contractual obligations, (c) it is necessary for us to comply with legal and/or regulatory requirements and/or (d) it is in our legitimate interests (e.g., we may use personal information for marketing, sales and customer service activities, to improve the Site and our services and to support our IT security efforts).

Retention of Personal Information:

We retain your personal information as long as necessary to provide you with our “services” (including the Site, mobile applications (if any), our products, events, programs and other services) and for other necessary purposes including: (a) complying with legal and regulatory requirements, (b) resolving disputes and (c) enforcing our rights and agreements.  The retention periods for different types of personal information may vary.  We consider the following criteria when determining applicable retention periods for personal information:

(a)           the nature of such personal information (sensitive personal information is typically kept for shorter periods);

(b)           our legal and contractual obligations to keep or delete such personal information;

(c)           the original purpose for our collection and processing of such personal information;

(d)           your ability to easily access, update and/or delete such personal information; and

(e)           whether you have consented to an extended retention period for such personal information.

Transfers of Personal Information:

Information regarding transfers of your personal information is included in the section of this Privacy Policy titled “International Users”.

Your GDPR Rights:

The GDPR provides the following additional rights to users located in the EEA, Switzerland and the UK (each subject to the limitations set forth in the GDPR):

(a)           the right to withdraw your consent for future processing of your personal information;

(b)           the right to request, access, correct and/or erase your personal information;

(c)           the right to data portability (the right to receive a copy of your personal information in a commonly used format); and

(d)           the right to restrict the processing of your personal information.

To exercise these rights, or if you have a question or complaint regarding our handling of your personal information, please contacting us at the email or mailing address listed in the “Contact Information” section of this Privacy Policy.

By clicking on the “Member Name” link at the top of the page you can access your personal account to make certain changes to your personal information.  You may also unsubscribe from any e-mail subscription by following the unsubscribe procedures set forth in each e-mail, including those received from our partners and affiliates.
